Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Okay. Mind your fingers.
Just like before now.
What you looking at?
What are we gonna do today?
Make yourself useful. and give it some thought.
Checkmate.
Okay.
Leave the crate and come straight back.
The weather looks like it's picking up.
Don't come up here again.
Most people just say thank you.
It's very important that you listen.
Don't ever come up here again.
You know. me and my uncle come up here
week after week. bringing you supplies.
and yet you never even come down to greet us.
Why is that?
I'm not afraid of you!
Message to all vessels.
Gale force winds are in serious effect
across the coast.
Jessie. come on!
New storm formed now heading
towards the Hebrides.
Don't give me that look.
Jessie!
Come on!
Papa!
Urgh!
Jessie!
Uh... argh!
Where's my uncle?
Where's my uncle?!
He's dead.
The trawler went down.
He was trapped.
Agh!
We need to get the swelling down.
Why haven't you called anyone
about what happened?
Not even the police.
Who else knows we're here?
No one?
Just rest.
You have to take me back.
You can't just keep me here.
I... I mean. I... I don't even
understand why you're here.
My uncle told me that this lighthouse
hasn't been working in years.
Yet you never leave here. Why?
My family will be looking for me.
You don't have a family.
Your mother died a few years back.
Never knew your father.
Your uncle's taken care of you ever since.
Because there was no one else.
How do you know that?
Well. someone will come looking.
Will they?
There's nothing here for anyone.
It's just a dream.
I know you're scared.
And in a lot of pain.
When you use a weapon.
you never operate from fear.
Always balance your emotions.
Keep your wits.
Hold it like this.
Your thumb up against the hilt.
Tight in the palm.
Hold it up.
Good.
That's a strong grip.
I'm gonna look at your ankle.
Come on.
How did you know my uncle?
We served together.
In the Royal Marines.
He never told me your name.
What is it?
Would it make a difference if you knew it?
Well. I'd at least know what to call you.
We're doing okay so far.
Well. at least tell me your dog's name then.
He doesn't have one.
What?
That's crazy.
Your dog doesn't even have a name?
Well...
I'm going to call him...
Jack.
Right. Jack? Come. Hey.
He likes the name Jack.
Jack.
Black Queen... to F2.
Check.
You didn't tell me you could play chess.
You never asked.
Looks like I've got myself a worthy opponent.
It's infected.
- Can't we just go to a hospital?
- No.
No.
I'll get what's needed.
Ten years ago. the Prime Minister
assured this committee and the nation
that her government. I quote...
"Was not and would not ever collect data
on British citizens."
And yet. thanks to the recent
hack into MI6's servers.
we have now learned that not only has MI6
been systematically harvesting
the personal information.
calls. emails. and voting patterns
of the British population.
but has been doing so in order
to create an intelligence...
super-system.
An advanced surveillance network
called Total Human Engagement Analytics.
or more affectionately. THEA.
Some of the details are. of course. classified.
The essence of THEA is to make
better-informed decisions.
to anticipate threats more effectively.
What you've been doing is
unlawfully invading the life
of every person in this country.
If they're innocent. they have nothing to hide.
Since THEA went online.
MI6 have intercepted threats
at a rate never before imagined.
Perhaps you could simply say thank you.
Let me be clear on how this ends.
With you and Prime Minister
Fordham under investigation.
and THEA dismantled.
Haneron was grandstanding. Prime Minister.
We both know the whole thing's a circus.
just without the entertainment value.
Haneron is gaining traction in this election.
And this leak...
it's a national embarrassment.
We're gonna have to steady the ship.
You need a sacrificial lamb.
Let's face it. Stephen.
You're probably the best spymaster
this country has ever produced.
But you are a hopeless bureaucrat.
We all have our shortcomings. Prime Minister.
The tape's stopped.
It's just the two of us now.
I think this could be a blessing.
Really?
To get you back into the shadows
where you belong.
Could be our little secret.
Indeed. Ma'am.
Roberta Frost. your number two.
she'll take over as head of MI6
as an interim appointment.
and then after the election.
I'll appoint somebody more appropriate.
Roberta's a good choice.
She's a good team player.
And we don't want any outsiders.
Exactly.
Enjoy your retirement.
Thank you. Prime Minister.
How old is she?
About there.
like I said we were supposed
to go in the first place. but I thought
we were gonna go bowling instead.
That's a bit more fun. no?
We always go...
like I said we were supposed
to go in the first place. but I thought
we were gonna go bowling instead.
That's a bit more fun. no?
High priority THEA alert.
We have a retinal match.
Timur Tchermoev.
He's a high value target. wanted for the bombing
of our embassy in Algeria.
His file is filled with similar atrocities.
Location?
Stornoway. Outer Hebrides.
Scotland.
Repositioning satellites now.
Who's our nearest assault team?
Alpha.
Send them.
Okay.
Let the medicine do its work.
That should be as good as new.
Thank you for the sweets. by the way.
I got these.
I hope they're okay.
It's the best I could do.
I like them.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mm.
Smells good.
So much better than porridge.
That. young lady. is a matter of opinion.
What?
What's happening?
Get in the bathroom.
Lock the door.
Don't make a sound.
Don't come out until I come for you.
Do it. Jessie.
Stay.
Weapons free.
Kill target on sight.
Agh...
Argh...
Find this fucker!
Oh. fuck!
Spread out. Box him in.
Argh!
Drop it! Jesus Christ!
I've found a girl.
Extracting her now.
Jack!
Argh!
Aaargh! Argh!
Let me go!
Argh!
Who is that? Who?
Who... who are these guys?
Who... yeah. who are...?
I need you to wait here.
Nothing's gonna happen.
I'm coming right back.
But... but where are you going?
Sorry. old boy.
I'm off the reservation.
With baggage.
Okay. I'll be there.
It's time to leave.
But w-what about Jack?
Come on.
Wha... what? What?
Jack? No. no!
Jack?
Come on. we need to leave.
Alpha team. come in.
They're all gone.
Who the hell is this guy?
Whoever he is. he's not Tchermoev.
Who's our nearest tier-one asset?
Workman.
Activate him.
And notify all QRF teams in
the region to be on standby.
Find out who that girl is.
Come on!
- You're hurt!
- I'll be fine.
But... but you're bleeding.
Come on.
Stay behind me.
I need to check something.
Wait here.
I need to go inside.
Get the keys.
You mean steal them?
Hey. I need you to wait here.
Ever use a gun?
I shot squirrels with my uncle's air rifle.
Good enough. Hold this.
One hand there. and one there.
Hold it tight against your body.
Keep the barrel pointed to the dirt.
Keep your finger off the trigger.
It's sensitive.
Get your back against the fence.
Hey. hey.
That's as far as you go.
Put it down.
Please.
Whoa!
Let's... let's go slow. hey?
He's hurt. Can you help him?
What am I looking at?
Timur Tchermoev.
His profile's been altered.
See here?
The code's been manipulated to hide someone else.
So. when a camera captures the real person.
it mis-identifies him as Tchermoev.
It's very sophisticated stuff.
Whoever did this used self-deleting code.
That's our guy.
Michael Mason.
He's one of ours?
Yeah.
But there aren't many details.
He... he was orphaned.
Former SBS operator.
K.I.A. ten years ago.
Apparently not.
Why would someone want to frame
one of our own to be targeted?
I don't know.
Whoa.
I... I just tried to access his
mission logs from Poole.
and I got this.
Okay. keep digging.
There's a man and a girl in our house.
Oh. the ops room just intercepted a 999 call
from a farm in Scotland.
matching Mason and our girl.
Call the ops room.
Let them know I'm on my way.
- We're all good. Sir.
- Thank you. Ross.
Shit.
They have guns...
Please help.
They're holding my father.
Our target is not who we thought.
His name is Michael Mason.
I want him caught and brought in for questioning.
- Where's my asset?
- Workman's en route.
Please. please help.
Workman.
Good.
Fuck you. Mason.
I'm... I'm not sure how good
this will hold.
I've only stitched goats and sheep.
I'm sure it's good.
Thanks.
We'll get out of your hair.
I'm gonna need your truck.
Keys are by the front door.
Go grab them. start it up.
I don't want you to hurt them.
I'm not gonna hurt them. Okay?
Where's your son?
Callum!
Did you just go do something?
Callum?
I called the police.
Let's move.
Come.
Sit there. Don't move.
Local authorities are responding
to a home invasion at the farm.
Well. tell them not to engage.
Hold a perimeter.
Do not engage.
I repeat do not engage!
We have personnel en route.
- Police!
- Are they going to arrest you?
It's not the police I'm worried about.
This way. Go. go. go.
Hey. hey. wait.
Don't open the door!
I live here...
Find out where those shots came from!
I'm sorry.
You need to stay here.
Come on.
Argh!
Put the weapon down!
Drop the weapon!
- Agh! Argh!
- Ugh! Urgh...
Come on.
Huh. uh!
Hey. police. Stop!
- Aargh!
- Drop the weapon!
One to echo.
We have multiple men down.
They're moving out.
- Hold your ground...
- Get in the back.
Keep your head down.
Get on Mason!
Patch me through to Workman!
He's turned off his comms.
What the fuck is going on?
Stay down and hold on.
Bravo two-one. we need backup immediately!
Ah! Uh...
Agh!
Ugh!
We're switching cars.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
Sir. stand still...
Hello. Roberta.
You calling to rub salt in the wound?
Hardly. Sir.
For what it's worth. I think the Prime Minister
sacking you was a grave misstep.
Flattery will get you everywhere.
How can I help you?
Does the name Michael Mason ring any bells?
Where did you hear that name?
He took down a full assault team...
alone.
What I'm about to say doesn't exist
outside of this conversation.
Years ago. we ran an off-book programme
of elite operatives called Black Kites.
Operatives untethered from MI6's oversight.
And Mason was one of them.
Yeah. He was one of the first.
He was a prodigy.
He became our gold standard.
Then what happened?
He was sent to eliminate
a foreign intelligence officer.
Instead. he spared the target.
falsified his report. and then disappeared.
Why would he defy orders?
We think he was turned.
I'm sure for a king's ransom.
You need to understand something.
Mason isn't just an assassin.
He's a precision instrument.
There's no stopping him.
You need to throw everything
you've got at him. Roberta.
Michael Mason unfortunately has become
a cancer on all that we stand for.
Yes. Sir.
Ready to put your trade craft to the test?
Am I gonna get fired for this?
Not unless I do.
I found the Black Kite files on a backup server.
Mason was helping an Iranian scientist defect
after he gave us everything
on their nuclear programme.
Instead of protecting him.
Mason was ordered to kill him for deniability.
It looks like he refused.
Good girl. Maddie.
Damn it. Roberta.
Some people just can't help themselves.
You okay?
You think I can't handle the truth
about who you really are. but I can.
Well... do you have family
somewhere?
No.
You never wanted one?
A wife. kids?
It complicates things.
I'd rather it be complicated then.
And have my mum back.
My uncle too.
Now I have no one.
I wish I could tell you
life would always be fair.
But you already know the truth to that.
No kid should have to go through what you did.
Just don't ever let it break your spirit.
No matter what.
Okay?
Here.
At least you had Jack.
He was your family.
Better you keep it.
Okay. there's a camera up
on the wall in front of us.
There's also one behind us.
I want you to get out on my side.
keep your head down and keep it forward.
So. when did you find religion?
Today...
when a ghost called me.
Oh. we have different interpretations
of what "baggage" means...
just saying.
Uh. no. that's the workshop.
Um...
I'm always building one thing or another.
Just be careful though.
there's lots of tools about.
Uh. Jessie?
Why don't you go get a drink?
The kitchen's in the back.
If you want me to leave so you guys can talk.
you can just say that.
Hey. hey...
It's okay.
Spirited girl.
Who is she?
What are you doing here?
Her uncle and I. we served together.
I need a way out... for her.
Then I'll start figuring out how they found me.
Don't tell me you've got
sentimental in your old age?
She's just a kid
who was in the wrong place at the wrong time.
Christ. Mason...
Meet THEA.
I helped build it before I left the circus.
The big question is...
how the hell did they find you
after I buried you?
Shit.
When it was time for you to disappear. I...
I changed your identity
to an oil worker in Aberdeen.
A nobody.
But someone figured it out.
and swapped it to this guy.
A high value terrorist on the watch list.
Which you know carries
an inter-agency kill order.
Manafort.
You... you really think he still
wants you dead
after all this time?
I broke the only rule that matters to him.
Fuck his rules.
You refused to kill an innocent man.
that you promised to help after he helped us.
Can you shut it down?
Not from here.
I mean. it wouldn't matter
anyway. You've been ID'd.
All those years on that island.
You should have stayed dead. Mason.
Yeah. that's my problem.
I just need you to keep Jessie safe.
Manafort knows who she is now...
which makes her a loose end.
You care about her. don't you?
This is where we part ways.
Can you keep her here?
Look. Mason. I... I can't.
Why?
He has cancer.
My mum took the same meds before she...
I'm sorry I'm such a drag to you.
Hey. Jessie. wait.
Is she right?
Doctors say I might get one more Christmas.
Oh. Jesus.
I'd help you if I could.
But you know I can't be responsible for her.
My hands are tied.
What if I go to Kamal?
He has the means to get her out...
- undetected.
- Kamal Shah?
No. No. no. no way.
- Not an option!
- Hey. look.
he's the best at what he does.
Yeah. because he's a violent trafficker.
And you haven't got MI6 behind
you to control him now.
Let me worry about that.
Just help me get to him.
Can you do that?
Listen. I... I can tell you
when to turn left or right.
That's about it.
Good enough.
Hey. Jessie... it's time to go.
Hey. Jessie. come on.
Were you really gonna leave me here?
I'm sorry.
Your safety is the most important thing to me.
Please.
Fine.
- Go stand by the wall.
- But...
Just do it!
Stand by the wall.
Jesus!
Hurgh!
Aaargh!
- Urgh!
- Argh!
Argh!
Let him go.
Just let him go.
Argh!
Come on!
Get here in now. go!
Go. go. get in!
Jesus!
Who was that?
Him.
20 years ago.
Ross?
We're doubling down. get your team ready.
Yes. Sir.
The Wi-Fi in there will suffice for my needs.
Here. take my hat and coat.
Help you hide those good looks.
Right.
Use only for an emergency.
or you know they'll trace you in a heartbeat.
Yeah. we're gonna have to switch motors.
They know we're in this one now.
You take care. young lady.
Thank you.
I wish you'd killed that man.
I know it's wrong to say that. but...
Maybe I'm becoming like you.
You're nothing like me. Jessie.
And I'm keeping it that way.
But how do you know?
Because I've seen who you really are.
Look... by tonight. all of this
will be behind you.
You'll start a brand-new life...
somewhere normal. somewhere safe.
And alone.
What will you do?
You can't go back to your island.
There's always another island.
I could come with you.
You don't want this life.
Always on the run. looking over your shoulder...
And you do?
Hey. Jessie. you need to understand.
The only way that I can protect you...
is to stop the people that are doing this.
You need to stay close to me. alright?
Any sign of Mason?
No. We have nothing.
He knows what h e's do in g.
You're right.
I found an unknown login to THEA
from outside MI6.
I have a bad feeling.
Can you ID?
No.
There is... there is something
I can try.
Whatever it is. do it quickly.
There's a camera. It'll see us.
Let's hope it's working.
Sorry. mate. Invite only.
Aargh!
Take me to Kamal.
or I'll break your other wrist.
Well played. Roberta.
My trap worked. I got him.
It's...
Oh. shit.
- That's...
- Stephen Manafort.
I know.
We'll deal with him later.
Get me every camera in this club. now!
Let's keep this walk nice and smooth.
Tell him it's Michael Mason.
Do you know Michael Mason. boss?
Michael Mason.
Look at you.
No country. no badge.
Just a poor bastard who thought
he had friends in the game.
Who's she?
I need a way out...
of the country for her. Tonight.
New identity.
Somewhere off grid.
No.
No?
How do you think you've been allowed to operate
for all these years. Kamal?
With impunity.
And with the luxury of getting
rid of your competition
at the same time.
By ratting them out to Manafort and I.
Manafort's gone.
Not gone...
unshackled.
He's more dangerous than ever to us both.
- You're lying.
- Am I?
The second the security camera
outside saw me walk in here.
into your club. every operative
MI6 has within 25 miles
was activated to bring me in.
I reckon you've got ten minutes. tops.
All I need is for you to get her out.
And I'll go cut the head off the snake.
Bury all our dirty little secrets with it.
Wait here.
Please come with me.
You heard the deal I made with him.
I need to honour my side.
Honour your side?
I think you wanna die.
What's that supposed to mean?
You don't think you have anything to live for.
If you really wanted to. you'd come!
Hey. people like me don't get to
go and live a normal life!
You keep telling yourself that.
Hey. hey...
- You're stronger than this.
- No. I'm not.
Yes. you are.
I need you to be.
Just promise me you're not going to die?
Exactly.
Right. where's my tactical team?
- En route.
- I want Mason and the girl
taken in alive.
They are not to open fire.
Car's out front.
How far out is your team?
They're still en route. Sir.
Where the fuck are you?
Thirty seconds out. Sir.
The girl is his Achille's heel.
Use that to your advantage.
Copy that. Sir.
Passport. ID and 20.000 euros.
She goes to our safe house in Spain for now.
Boat leaves Isle of Dogs
in 30 minutes. It won't wait.
Just make sure you finish what you started.
If you handle your end. I'll handle mine.
Wait on the other side of the square.
Let's move. Alright. let's go.
This is Zulu. two minutes out.
Do we have an exact location inside?
Wait. you're not already there?
That's a negative.
Manafort. Tell them that there's
a rogue team already inside.
They need to get in there now!
Now!
Argh!
I've got you.
Mason!
Arthur. Manafort's guards
have got Jessie.
Move. move. move.
Out of the way! Out the way!
Found her. Hold on.
Out the front entrance.
Cut across the square and turn south.
She's being carried towards a black transit van.
I've got her! Move. move!
Go. go. go!
Get ready!
He's gonna be coming for her!
Get in there!
Where are you going?
I don't see Mason.
There!
Mason's heading right towards you.
Move!
Fucking move!
I got you.
It's okay.
I got you. Jessie.
I got you.
You okay?
Time to go.
There's your ride.
Hey.
You're gonna be okay.
Come on.
Gonna lower her down.
You've gotta hurry!
- Ready? It's time to go.
- No.
- The boat won't wait.
- No. no. no. You...
You said you can't live
a normal life. but you're wrong.
You just have to come on the boat with me
and we can... we can disappear
and we can have a normal life.
- Please. No. please! Please!
- The boat won't wait.
You're all I have now!
I don't wanna leave you.
Hey. Jessie.
- No!
- Listen to me.
- Jessie.
- No!
This is the only way I can keep you safe.
I'm sorry.
No! I'm not... I'm not leaving
without you!
I have to save you!
You saved me already.
Come on.
- Now. Jessie!
- No!
Okay. she's safe.
No. no. please!
Do you even know why you're doing this?
Does it matter?
You can't save her either.
Argh!
Newly appointed MI6 head. Roberta Frost.
is dealing with the fallout...
You were my dearest...
my greatest weapon.
And then you broke the rules.
Black Kites know one law
above all: loyalty.
You put your conscience first
and the mission second.
I finally put humanity over blind obedience.
Oh. yeah. There it is.
The righteous martyr.
And a foolish one. You allowed
a civilian into this game.
A child! What good is
all that humanity
with her blood on your hands?
That's not gonna happen.
And you know it.
I don't want that either.
You really think you can outrun what you are?
We are who we are. Mason.
I have been given complete autonomy
to make Black Kites stronger than ever.
I want you with me... by my side.
as we were.
You're the very reason I didn't
pull the trigger ten years ago.
And why I have to now.
What's up? Anything new?
Just having some cocoa and reading a book.
Zoom in and up-res.
Er. maybe we should start exploring
other ways to find him.
He hid from us for ten years...
until her.
It's a matter of when.
Wait.
It's him.
Your friend said this was for you.
- Where is he?
- He was there a moment ago.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org